this tutorial is about palm strips these
本教程是关于棕榈条
是二维运动，也称为
this tutorial is about palm strips these
are two-dimensional motions also called
互动机制，这是最
简单，只需拉动标签即可
are two-dimensional motions also called
interactive mechanisms this is the most
改变在窗户后面，这是
基本的拉条，具有各种
interactive mechanisms this is the most
simple as you pull the tab the image
我将向您展示最多的应用程序
基本的，这是另一个例子
simple as you pull the tab the image
changes behind the window this is the
比这里的其他人更容易看到
再次，你的形象改变了
changes behind the window this is the
basic pull strip that has all sorts of
窗户后面的事实是你有
用这些去思考
basic pull strip that has all sorts of
applications I'll just show you the most
剥离本身，然后方向
运动受这两个因素支配
applications I'll just show you the most
basic so here's another example that's
袖子我待会儿解释
然后在页面上切开缝
basic so here's another example that's
easier to see than the other one here
他们控制着方向
缝隙的运动你也有一个标签
easier to see than the other one here
again you've got the image changing
控制运动量
这条，你可以有一个
again you've got the image changing
behind the window the fact is you have
像我在这里做的那样内置
其实只是贴一张卡
behind the window the fact is you have
to think about with these are the full
像这样越过
它会前进并遇到
to think about with these are the full
strip itself and then the direction of
页面上的这个缝隙我会放一个
现在在一起，你可以看到它如何
strip itself and then the direction of
movement is governed by these two
实际去
这些都用卷尺测量，所以我不得不
movement is governed by these two
sleeves I'll explain those in a minute
测量并事先准备
而不是袖手旁观
sleeves I'll explain those in a minute
and this slit the slit in the page so
这是实际的地带
这两个图像要去哪里
and this slit the slit in the page so
they control the direction of the
使地带强记下来
中间然后折痕而不是
they control the direction of the
movement of the slit you also have a tab
只是将两块层压在一起
有折痕然后粘上你
movement of the slit you also have a tab
that controls the amount of movement of
如果只是，则获得更强的剥离
然后拉就没关系了
that controls the amount of movement of
this strip and you can either have one
单一厚度的卡片，但是因为您
将不得不拉它，推你
this strip and you can either have one
built in like I've done here or you can
希望它真的粘在一起
否则会弯曲
built in like I've done here or you can
actually just stick a piece of card
所以这是你的拉力条，我会粘上它
一起吧
actually just stick a piece of card
across like that so that as you pull it
这是要去的工作表
在上面，所以我已经在其中切开了窗户
across like that so that as you pull it
it'll move along and come up against
这些是两个地方
袖子要适合这是
it'll move along and come up against
this slit in the page I'll put one
切开东西通过，所以我会
剪掉其中一个时就剪一下
this slit in the page I'll put one
together now so you can see how it
缝隙将其削减了几个MIL
两端，以便卡可以抬起
together now so you can see how it
actually goes
如此轻微地上升
整个事情要动得多
these do tape measuring so I've had to
容易，所以这些就是你的袖子
两个折痕使每个折痕一个
these do tape measuring so I've had to
measure it and prepare it beforehand
图像的窗口侧面
将会出现，所以折痕这些
measure it and prepare it beforehand
rather than just doing it off the cuff
很好地把它粘下来，但是这些你
不需要太多胶水，或者您想要
rather than just doing it off the cuff
here this is the actual strip this is
像这样粘着的任何东西
需要确保您让它干燥，因为
here this is the actual strip this is
where the two images are going to go to
如果渗出的胶确实粘了
工作，事情做得不好
where the two images are going to go to
make the strip strong score it down the
这是一个袖子，这是另一个
我已经在需要的地方评分了
make the strip strong score it down the
middle then crease it so rather than
折叠，然后添加胶水
粘在小卡片上而不是
middle then crease it so rather than
just laminating two pieces together by
大一个，所以这个袖子很小
底座很大，所以你把
just laminating two pieces together by
having a crease and then gluing it you
将胶水粘在套筒上
现在，如果我们看看拉线
having a crease and then gluing it you
get a far stronger strip if it was just
本身将适合这种方式
你会发现这些袖子必须
get a far stronger strip if it was just
pulling then it doesn't matter if it's
比...宽几毫米
条本身在每一侧，所以他们
pulling then it doesn't matter if it's
single thickness card but because you're
实际上并没有抓住它，所以他们要去
当您关闭它时可以像这样折叠
single thickness card but because you're
going to have to pull it and push it you
下来，您只需要最小的DAB
胶水，所以我在这里戳一下
going to have to pull it and push it you
want it to be stuck together really
第一
现在可以轻松轻松地移动了
want it to be stuck together really
strong otherwise it will tend to buckle
此面朝下放下最小
胶水轻轻一点，所以没有压力
strong otherwise it will tend to buckle
so this is your pull strip I'll glue it
它不需要太多的胶水
是它不会渗出和粘在
so this is your pull strip I'll glue it
together right
工作，所以这是一个袖子，这是
另一个
here's the sheet that it's going to go
那里有一点点胶
关闭它，这是拉带
here's the sheet that it's going to go
on so I've already cut the window in it
动作这是最神奇的
罗伯特的捉迷藏计数书
on so I've already cut the window in it
these are the places where the two
克劳斯（Krauser）是一本非常古老的书，但是有一本
很多这样的事情，所以
these are the places where the two
sleeves are going to fit this is the
我想告诉你的是这一个
你实际上已经把这个拉了
sleeves are going to fit this is the
slit that the thing goes through so I'll
剥离它出来，它出来
页面并在您下移下
slit that the thing goes through so I'll
just cut this when you cut one of these
放它，你可以看到有一张图片
在这里在窗户后面改变
just cut this when you cut one of these
slits cut it back a couple of MIL at
有一个形象下降的采访
那里还有另外一对
slits cut it back a couple of MIL at
each end so that the card can just lift
这是尼娜·坎尼（Nina Canny）的变色龙莱昂
AK，这是这里
each end so that the card can just lift
up ever so slightly that makes it the
拉条，拉动就可以看到
图像改变还有另一种
up ever so slightly that makes it the
whole thing just move that much more
拉条的这种是这种的
真的很粗糙
whole thing just move that much more
easily so these are the sleeves you have
在页面上放一个插槽，然后拉动
拉条它将图像向下移动
easily so these are the sleeves you have
two creases stick them down one on each
页，如果我们查看所有内容的背面
您需要再次在页面中缝
two creases stick them down one on each
side of the window that the images are
它被略微削减以使其
移动方便，但施工
side of the window that the images are
going to appear in so just crease these
在这里固定它的长度
插槽决定移动的距离
going to appear in so just crease these
quite well glue it down but these you
我将很快使其中之一成为现实
所以只要拿一张卡得分
quite well glue it down but these you
don't want too much glue or you want to
剪了它
将它折成两半移动，但是有一个
don't want too much glue or you want to
anything you're gluing like this you
拉条准备走了，现在我们需要一个
它将适合的插槽
anything you're gluing like this you
need to make sure you let it dry because
再次，你需要你需要削减它
这次用尺子真的让我
need to make sure you let it dry because
if the glue oozing it does gum up the
这样的插槽，并使其退回两个或
三毫米宽再切
if the glue oozing it does gum up the
works and things don't work so well so
剪掉，然后你要
最后需要一个缝所以
works and things don't work so well so
that's one sleeve this is the other
从那有多宽和公正来判断
这样碰到两个
that's one sleeve this is the other
I've already scored it where it needs to
小削减，现在到关键
你只需要一块这样的东西
I've already scored it where it needs to
fold and you're adding glue always put
您将其粘贴到所需的拉条上
进来闭嘴，你要
fold and you're adding glue always put
glue on the small piece of card not the
有两个这样的小块
通过插槽关闭，所以这是
glue on the small piece of card not the
big one so this sleeve is the small bit
另一边，是的，所以这两个目的
将通过插槽站起来
big one so this sleeve is the small bit
and the base is the big bit so you put
我们也会把那些胶粘下来
在这下面放些胶水
and the base is the big bit so you put
the glue onto the sleeve stick it in
这是非常快速和粗鲁的
稍微修剪一下就喂
the glue onto the sleeve stick it in
place now if we look at the pull strip
通过另一端出现
通过那里，他们折叠起来，你可以
place now if we look at the pull strip
itself it's going to fit around this way
粘上您的图像
这两个
itself it's going to fit around this way
around you'll see these sleeves have to
然后你有一块滑动
像这样在页面上下
around you'll see these sleeves have to
be a couple of millimeters wider than
这里有一个变化
这是我刚刚制作的主要作品
be a couple of millimeters wider than
the strip itself on each side so they
但这是一条带有三个折痕的条
在这一点上，这是粘在
the strip itself on each side so they
don't actually grip it so they're going
相当于这个目的
到页面，所以当您拉动它时
don't actually grip it so they're going
to fold over like this when you close it
这个上升的3D形状还有另一个
我实际上在这里卡住的一个
to fold over like this when you close it
down you just need the smallest dab of
掩盖下来的作品，所以这一作为
你拉它，你看到下巴下降和
down you just need the smallest dab of
glue so I'll just poke it through here
眼睛改变了我实际上所做的
在我完全了解这种机制之前
glue so I'll just poke it through here
first
所以当你看的时候，你会看到
放下有两个荡妇
first
that moves nice and easy now we can take
不必要，你只需要一个我
很像面具的想法
that moves nice and easy now we can take
this side close it down put the smallest
碰到并隐藏所有工作原理
这样您就可以更加愉快了
this side close it down put the smallest
dab of glue there's no stress on this so
机制所有这些东西都被覆盖
在我最近的书的弹出式设计中
dab of glue there's no stress on this so
it doesn't need much glue the main thing
纸力学，它确实需要拉力
去除一点，但真正的细节
it doesn't need much glue the main thing
is that it doesn't ooze and gum up the
在这本较早的书中可以弹出一个
纸机制手册，这是
is that it doesn't ooze and gum up the
work so that's one sleeve and here's the
进一步了解拉带
实际上已经绝版了，但是我认为
work so that's one sleeve and here's the
other one
可能获得二手版本